Muhammad Zhafir Ghiffari

South Tangerang, Indonesia 15412 | Muhammad Zhafir Ghiffari | 087782465900 | m.zhafirghiffari@gmail.com

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

A software engineer with experience designing, developing, and maintaining web-based applications. Experienced as a web developer in government agencies for 1 year. Experience with PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript. Have a strong desire to learn new things in the world of software engineering.

EXPERIENCES

PUSTEKINFO DPR RI

Web Developer

(January 2022 - February 2023)

- Create a web-based application that is used by DPR RI employees in preparation for plenary meetings.
- Create a web-based application that is used to perform electronic signatures for DPR RI employees.

CSEAS Indonesia

IT Support

(June 2021 - August 2021)

Assist employees in installing applications and entering and updating data in office databases.

EDUCATION

Bina Nusantara University
Bachelors Computer Science

(November 2019 - Present)

3,09

SKILLS

HTML (8), PHP (7), CSS (7), JavaScript (5), UI/UX Design (7), Laravel (7).

CERTIFICATIONS

Internship Certificate Sekretariat Jenderal DPR RI Sekretariat Jenderal DPR RI

February 2023

Apprentice Certificate in Information Systems and Information Technology Infrastructure of the Republic of Indonesia DPR